wpbeaverbuilder.com 2019-07-07

# Privacy Policy | Beaver Builder

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

### To personalize your experience

Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

### To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

### To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

## How can I determine what information you have?

If you wish to confirm that we are processing your personal data, or to have access to the personal data we may have about you, please contact us at info@fastlinemedia.com.

You may also request information about the purpose of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned, who might have received the data from us, what the source of the information was (if you didn’t provide it directly to us), and how long it will be stored. You have a right to correct the record of your personal data maintained by us if it is inaccurate. You may request that we erase that data or cease processing it, subject to certain exceptions. You may also request that we cease using your data for direct marketing purposes. In many countries, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we process your personal data. When technically feasible, we will, at your request, provide your personal data to you or transmit it directly to another controller.

Reasonable access to your personal data will be provided at no cost upon request made to us at info@fastlinemedia.com. If access cannot be provided within a reasonable timeframe, we will provide you with a date when the information will be provided. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation as to why access has been denied.

## What rights do I have regarding how my data is collected and used?

You have the following rights regarding our retention and processing of your personal data:

### Account Information & Retention

You may update, correct, or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account and modifying your information or by emailing us at info@fastlinemedia.com. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. If you wish to deactivate your account, please email us at info@fastlinemedia.com, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our customers as directed. We will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce agreements.

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information that we are aware of. To request this information, contact us at info@fastlinemedia.com.

### Promotional and Newsletter Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional and newsletter emails from us by following the opt-out instructions provided in those emails. You may also opt-out of receiving promotional emails and other promotional communications from us at any time by emailing info@fastlinemedia.com with your specific request. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as security alerts and notices related to your access to or use of our services or those about your online account or our ongoing business relations.

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies or to prompt you before accepting such a cookie. Please note that, if you choose to remove or reject browser cookies, this could affect the availability or functionality of our services.

### California Residents

You may choose to opt out of our disclosure of personal information about you to third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you choose to opt-out at any time after granting approval email info@fastlinemedia.com.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database, that is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personal information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Newsletter

By becoming a member of Beaver Builder, you acknowledge and agree to be signed up for our newsletter which will be sent to you occasionally for either bug releases, theme updates, or when new items are released. You are free to opt-out at any time by clicking on the link provided in the newsletter. We do not give your personal information to any 3rd party companies as mentioned in our Privacy Policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you more directly by email or means of a notice on the home page prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you access our services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy and do not wish your information to be subject to the revised Privacy Policy, you will need to deactivate with us and stop using our services. Your use of any of our services after the posting of such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.

This policy was last modified on 05/23/2018.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below:

FastLine Media LLC  
2443 Fillmore Street, Suite 380-5288  
San Francisco, CA 94115, USA  
info@fastlinemedia.com
